tresta.com 2016-09-11

# Privacy Policy | Tresta

Tresta, Inc. Privacy Statement

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

This privacy policy applies to you. Basically, if you are on our site or use our services, it applies to you. 

## Tresta, Inc. Privacy Statement

At Tresta, Inc. ("Tresta"), we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use our websites, products and services. This privacy statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. Personal information is any information that identifies you or would enable someone to contact you, such as your name, email address, phone number and other non-public information that is associated with such information. This privacy statement applies to all services provided by Tresta. Tresta is located at 2639 North Monroe Street, Suite 200B, Tallahassee, Florida 32303. Summary sentences provided on our website are provided to help you better understand our privacy policy, but do not represent the entirety of the privacy policy.

Information We Collect

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

We collect lots of information about you for a variety of different reasons. 

## Information We Collect

The following identifies the categories of personally identifiable information that we collect about our customers. We collect customer names, addresses, phone numbers, website addresses, email addresses, credit card information, and an authorization question and answer for customers and any authorized contacts designated on a customer account. We may also collect information about the technology you use to access the Tresta platform, such as a browser, IP address, or operating system.

Keeping in Touch

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

If you don't want to hear from us, tell us! We'll respect your request. 

## Keeping in Touch

Tresta collects email addresses from all current customers, visitors to our websites, and individuals who request information from us by phone, online chat, or email. Tresta gives you the option to discontinue receiving marketing emails from us. Every marketing email we send has an opt-out URL, so that you can unsubscribe whenever you want. You cannot opt out of receiving emails related to account status changes or billing information, such as a billing statement, receipt, or credit card charge attempt.

Use of Personal Information

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

Tresta will never sell your personal information to others. We will share it when needed to support your account or run our own analytics, but not so others can try and sell you their stuff too. 

## Use of Personal Information

We will treat your personal information as confidential, and we will not share it with third parties without your permission, except in the limited circumstances described below.

We may provide your personal information to third parties for purposes of billing, charging your credit card, and determining the applicable taxes and regulatory fees that may apply to your services. We may also provide your personal information to third parties that perform customer support functions, including communicating with you directly through email or online chat platforms. We may share your personal information with third parties for purposes of sending marketing or promotional materials to you related exclusively to Tresta products or services. We do not sell or rent personal information to third parties, and we do not share your personal information with third parties who wish to use it for the purposes of marketing non-Tresta products or services.

Protection of Personal Information

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

We try very hard to protect your personal information by keeping up with current standards of security, but you should know – nothing over the internet is 100% guaranteed safe. 

## Protection of Personal Information

The security of your personal information is important to us. We do not store customer credit card account information. Credit card account numbers are encrypted and stored by a third party that specializes in the collection and maintenance of credit card information. All personal information, other than credit card numbers, is stored in a protected database that is accessible by a limited number of Tresta employees. All servers that store customer data have undergone a process known as "security hardening" to improve security and reduce the vulnerability of data stored on the servers consistent with best practices and National Security Agency guidelines. Customer data may be stored in data centers provided by third parties. All third-party data centers are compliant with current industry standards. While we follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is one hundred percent secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Please contact us if you have any questions about the security of our services.

Tresta.com uses Google Display Advertising data to improve the experience of our website for our users. These display features enable Google to collect data about our users via Google advertising cookies, anonymous identifiers and other data collected through Google's standard analytics implementation. We respect your privacy and if you wish, you may opt-out of [Google's tracking features](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) at any time.

Control of Personal Information

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

You can update your personal information at any time, but you should know that copies of the old and current information may be kept in our databases so that we can do things like conduct analysis or comply with legal requests. 

## Control of Personal Information

You can confirm, change, delete or update your personal information you have provided to us by logging into your account and going to the Edit Profile page, or by contacting customer service 24 hours a day/7 days a week.

Please note that, even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users. We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services and after the termination of your account for analytical purposes and/or to reactivate your account if you elect to do so. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Protection of Children's Privacy

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

We don't want to keep information about children under the age of 13, but if we find out that we have, we'll delete it. 

## Protection of Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect any personally identifying information from people under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without such parent or guardian's consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.

Use of Cookies

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

Tresta uses cookies for a variety of reasons, and so do some of our third party service providers. 

## Use of Cookies

When you visit our site we may store information about your web session and assign you one or more cookies. Your browser will store these cookies on your computer in a small text file, and if you return to the site the cookie may be read. Cookies are linked to your personal information. Permanent cookie files remain on your computer's hard drive until you delete them manually using your browser or operating system software. The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. In some circumstances third parties may track and collect personally identifiable information about our users on our behalf.

Notification of Changes

Basically the Lawyers Are Saying:

This privacy policy isn't set in stone – it can change if needed, but we'll notify you anytime we make changes. 

## Notification of Changes

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to change this privacy statement in any material way, we will notify you here, by email, or by other means so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. In all cases, your continued use of any Site or our products and services constitutes consideration and your binding acceptance to any such changes.
